

ABOUT ME

I am an enthusiastic and creative person with extensive experience working in high pressure environments where meeting deadlines is key. I am adept at communicating with stakeholders across all levels of complex organisations. Having worked in teaching for four years, I am now keen to gain experience in the field of sales and feel that the skills and experience gained from recent roles will equip me to excel.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATES

Kingston University Digital Skills: User Experience

BA (Hons) Illustration Animation

Accenture

Consumer Behaviour and Psychology

Coventry University - Online

2013 - 2016

2020

2020

EXPERIENCE

Manager

Enjoy Expressing English

September 2021 - Present

- Direct line management of two team members
- Responsible for overall development of team members and ensuring their targets were met
- Commended by senior staff for creating exceptional lesson plans
- Improved behaviour of the class by implementing classroom management techniques
- Prepared students to take Cambridge Certificate English exams achieving a high pass rate
- Improved the appearance of the school by designing and creating artwork and props
- Distributed flyers and spoke with potential new customers at diverse locations across Madrid, selling the benefits of the summer school and winning 5 new customers

English Teacher

IES Vega del Jarama

Colegio Bienaventurada Virgen María / Colegio San José Moreno Nieto

October 2019 - June 2021

September 2018 - June 2019

- Created lesson plans to engage high school learners, including classes about English grammar, literature and culture from English speaking countries
- Taught English and other subjects in the bilingual program including Physics and Chemistry, P.E and Music
- Designed Cambridge Certificate exam preparation classes
- Led or co-taught classes with other teachers in the school

Team Member

MeatLiquor July 2017 - April 2018

- Interacted and communicated with customers
- Kept customer relationships strong by solving any problems and ensuring they want to return
- Upsold our products increasing spend per customer
- Memorised our extensive and changing menu
- Was named personally for providing excellent service by a restaurant reviewer

VOLUNTARY AND EXTRA - CURRICULAR

Founder and Chef

Con's Hot Sauces February 2021 - Present

- Researched the existing market of hot sauces in Spain
- Developed recipes and tested on peers
- Designed branding for labels and social media
- Used social media to create buzz about the business and find new customers
- Sold independently and created a returning customer base
- Sold on average 20 hot sauces per batch

Head of Marketing - Volunteer Position

Kingston University

January 2016 - June 2016

- Took on the leadership role in the marketing team in the organisation of our final year degree show
- Created and ran social media pages which were essential for promotion and advertising
- Created and ran a successful Kickstarter campaign, raising £2000
- Understood the importance of keeping the branding and visual language consistent
- · Researched, identified and invited influential names within the art and design industry
- Identified and delegated tasks to the rest of the marketing team

SKILLS

- Leadership and teamwork
- Public speaking
- Creative thinking and problem solving
- Customer service
- Excellent communication

LANGUAGES

English

Native

Spanish

Intermediate